Applied and decorative arts photograph collection (medals-musical instruments).
Yale University Arts Library
- Ivories. (Box 55)
  - Romanesque to Modern., 105 (Box 60)
    - Iceland., 1 (Box 62)
    - Italy., 12 (Box 62)
      - Unknown Artists., 9 (Box 62)
      - Known Artists., 3 (Box 62)
        - Baldassare degli Embriachi, active 1390., 3 (Box 62)
    - Spain., 7 (Box 62)
- Jewelry. (Box 63)
  - Miscellaneous works., 1 (Box 63)
  - Egyptian., 12 (Box 63)
  - Countries., 18 (Box 63)
    - Austria., 3 (Box 63)
      - Unknown Artists., 1 (Box 63)
      - Known Artists., 2 (Box 63)
        - Hoffmann, Josef, 1870-1918., 1 (Box 63)
        - Mucha, Alphonse, 1880-1969., 1 (Box 63)
    - France., 11 (Box 63)
      - Unknown Artists., 1 (Box 63)
      - Known Artists., 10 (Box 63)
        - Bing, Marcel, XIX-XX C., 1 (Box 63)
        - Lalique, Rene, 1860-1945., 8 (Box 63)
        - Sandoz, Gerard, 1902-., 1 (Box 63)
    - Germany., 1 (Box 63)
      - Known Artists., 1 (Box 63)
        - Saur, Corvinianus, -1735., 1 (Box 63)
    - India., 1 (Box 63)
    - Italy., 1 (Box 63)
    - United States., 1 (Box 63)
      - Known Artists., 1 (Box 63)
        - Kerr, William B. and Co., 1855-1906., 1 (Box 63)
- Lacquer. (Box 63)
  See also: Furniture.
  - Persia., 2 (Box 63)
  - England., 1 (Box 63)
  - France., 1 (Box 63)
- Leather. (Box 63)
  - Italy., 1 (Box 63)
- Manuscripts. (Box 64)
  - Miscellaneous works., 1 (Box 64)
  - Islamic., 161 (Box 64)
    - Miscellaneous works., 1 (Box 64)
    - Persia., 160 (Box 64)
      - Miscellaneous works., 10 (Box 64)
      - XIII Century., 16 (Box 64)
      - XIV Century., 19 (Box 64)
      - XV Century., 36 (Box 65)
        - Miscellaneous works., 32 (Box 65)
        - School of Behrad., 4 (Box 65)
          Name also given as Behzad and Bihzad.
      - XVI Century., 46 (Box 66)
        - Miscellaneous works., 41 (Box 66)
        - School of Sultan Muhammed., 3 (Box 66)
        - Muhammed d'Ali., 2 (Box 66)
      - XVII Century., 14 (Box 66)
      - XVIII Century., 15 (Box 66)
      - XIX Century., 4 (Box 66)
  - Egypt., 2 (Box 67)
  - Greek and Roman., 24 (Box 67)
  - Early Christian., 95 (Box 67)
    - Miscellaneous works., 1 (Box 67)
    - IV to V Century., 5 (Box 67)
    - VI Century., 54 (Box 67)
      - Miscellaneous works., 15 (Box 67)
      - MS Syriac 33., 8 (Box 67)
      - London Canon Tables, MS 5111., 4 (Box 67)
      - Rabula Gospels., 12 (Box 67)
      - Rossano Gospels., 15 (Box 67)
    - VIII to IX Century., 19 (Box 68)
      - Miscellaneous works., 7 (Box 68)
      - MS 7169., 12 (Box 68)
    - VIII to X Century., 16 (Box 68)
      - MS Petropol 21., 16 (Box 68)
  - Byzantine., 82 (Box 68)
    - Miscellaneous works., 18 (Box 68)
    - X Century., 18 (Box 69)
      - Miscellaneous works., 4 (Box 69)
      - Joshua Roll., 3 (Box 69)
      - Paris Psalter., 11 (Box 69)
    - XI Century., 26 (Box 69)
      - Miscellaneous works., 9 (Box 69)
      - MS Add. 19352., 2 (Box 69)
      - MS Coislin 79., 3 (Box 69)
      - MS Grec 543., 1 (Box 69)
      - MS Grec 550., 9 (Box 69)
      - MS Petropol 305., 2 (Box 69)
    - XII Century., 11 (Box 69)
    - XIII Century., 3 (Box 69)
      - Miscellaneous works., 2 (Box 69)
      - MS Grec 923., 1 (Box 69)
    - XIV Century., 6 (Box 69)
      - Miscellaneous works., 3 (Box 69)
      - MS Curzon 153., 3 (Box 69)
  - Crusader., 14 (Box 69)
  - Coptic., 88 (Box 70-, Box 71)
    - Miscellaneous works., 2 (Box 71)
    - XII Century., 86 (Box 71)
      - MS Copte 13., 86 (Box 71)
  - Celtic., 93 (Box 72)
    - Miscellaneous works., 15 (Box 72)
    - Book of Durrow., 9 (Box 72)
    - Echternach Gospels., 9 (Box 72)
    - Book of Kells., 17 (Box 72)
    - Lindisfarne Gospels., 16 (Box 72)
    - Gospels of Maseyck., 19 (Box 72)
      Also spelled Maaseik.
    - Stockholm Gospels., 5 (Box 72)
      Also known as the Codex Aureus.
    - S. Chad Gospels., 3 (Box 72)
  - Merovingian., 3 (Box 72)
  - Carolingian., 228 (Box 73)
    - Miscellaneous works., 16 (Box 73)
    - Cambrai Apocalypse., 42 (Box 73)
    - MS 61 at Wolfenbuttel., 22 (Box 74)
    - Charlemagne Court School., 17 (Box 74)
      - Miscellaneous works., 9 (Box 74)
      - Godescalc Gospels, 781-783., 8 (Box 74)
    - Charles the Bald Court School., 13 (Box 74)
      - Miscellaneous works., 2 (Box 74)
      - Bible of S. Paolo, c.870., 6 (Box 74)
      - Golden Gospels of S. Emmeram, 870., 5 (Box 74)
    - Franco-Saxon School., 20 (Box 74)
      - Miscellaneous works., 14 (Box 74)
      - Gospel Book of S. Vaast., 6 (Box 74)
    - Reims School., 53 (Box 75)
      - Miscellaneous works., 23 (Box 75)
      - Ebbo Gospels, 816-835., 24 (Box 75)
      - Physiologus, c.825-850., 6 (Box 75)
    - Tours School., 40 (Box 76)
      - Miscellaneous works., 5 (Box 76)
      - Vivian Bible, c.846., 6 (Box 76)
      - MS Latin 267., 11 (Box 76)
      - MS at Laon., 18 (Box 76)
    - S. Gall School., 5 (Box 76)
  - Romanesque., 1 (Box 76)
  - Countries., 1381 (Box 77)
    - Abyssinia., 3 (Box 77)
    - Armenia., 17 (Box 77)
    - Austria., 13 (Box 77)
    - Britain., 217 (Box 78)
      - Miscellaneous works., 6 (Box 78)
      - XI Century., 5 (Box 78)
      - XII Century., 53 (Box 78)
        - Miscellaneous works., 10 (Box 78)
        - Cambridge., 12 (Box 78)
          - Miscellaneous works., 4 (Box 78)
          - Eadwine Psalter, c.1100-1150., 8 (Box 78)
        - London., 24 (Box 78)
          - Miscellaneous works., 1 (Box 78)
          - Lambeth Bible., 7 (Box 78)
          - British Museum., 16 (Box 78)
            - Miscellaneous works., 4 (Box 78)
            - Cotton MS Nero C IV., 7 (Box 78)
            - Cotton MS Caligula A VII., 5 (Box 78)
        - New York., 7 (Box 78)
      - XIII Century., 95 (Box 79)
        - Miscellaneous works., 20 (Box 79)
        - Cambridge., 10 (Box 79)
        - London., 65 (Box 79)
          - British Museum., 58 (Box 79)
            - Miscellaneous works., 25 (Box 79)
            - Psalter, Royal MS 1.D X, before 1220., 7 (Box 80)
            - Westminster Abbey Psalter, Royal MS 2A XXII., 13 (Box 80)
            - Bestiary, MS Harley 4751., 6 (Box 80)
            - Psalter, MS Add. 49622., 7 (Box 80)
          - Society of Antiquaries., 7 (Box 80)
      - XIV Century., 34 (Box 81)
        - Miscellaneous works., 7 (Box 81)
        - Brussels, Peterborough Psalter., 4 (Box 81)
        - London., 14 (Box 81)
          - Miscellaneous works., 7 (Box 81)
          - Psalter of Robert de Lisle, Arundel MS 83., 7 (Box 81)
        - New York., 9 (Box 81)
      - XV Century., 22 (Box 81)
      - XVII Century., 1 (Box 81)
      - XIX Century., 1 (Box 81)
    - Ethiopia., 2 (Box 82)
    - Flanders., 183 (Box 82)
      - Miscellaneous works., 18 (Box 82)
      - XV Century., 135 (Box 82)
        - Miscellaneous works., 42 (Box 82)
        - Brussels., 57 (Box 83)
          - Miscellaneous works., 50 (Box 83)
          - La Fleur des Histoires, MS 9231., 4 (Box 83)
          - Chroniques de Hainaut, MS 9242., 3 (Box 83)
        - London., 16 (Box 83)
        - Venice., 20 (Box 83)
          - Grimani Breviary., 20 (Box 83)
      - XVI Century., 30 (Box 84)
    - France., 521 (Box 85)
      - Miscellaneous works., 10 (Box 85)
      - XI Century., 44 (Box 85)
        - Miscellaneous works., 28 (Box 85)
        - Psalter of Odbert, c.1000., 16 (Box 85)
      - XII Century., 21 (Box 85)
      - XIII Century., 53 (Box 86)
        - Miscellaneous works., 21 (Box 86)
        - London., 6 (Box 86)
        - New York., 16 (Box 86)
          - Miscellaneous works., 4 (Box 86)
          - Bible Moralise, 1226-1239, MS 240., 7 (Box 86)
          - Old Testament, 1230-1250, MS 638., 5 (Box 86)
        - Paris., 10 (Box 86)
          - Miscellaneous works., 4 (Box 86)
          - Psalter of S. Louis, 1253-1270, MS Latin 10525., 6 (Box 86)
      - XIV Century., 79 (Box 87)
        - Miscellaneous works., 17 (Box 87)
        - London., 11 (Box 87)
        - New York., 11 (Box 87)
          - Miscellaneous works., 6 (Box 87)
          - Hours of Jeanne d'Evreux, Pucelle, Jean, active 1319-1358., 5 (Box 87)
        - Paris., 40 (Box 87)
          - Miscellaneous works., 29 (Box 87)
          - Grandes Chroniques de France, MS Fr. 2813., 7 (Box 87)
          - Belleville Breviary, Pucelle, Jean, 1343, MS Latin 10483., 4 (Box 87)
      - XV Century., 300 (Box 88)
        - Miscellaneous works., 62 (Box 88)
        - Brussels., 17 (Box 89)
          - Miscellaneous works., 10 (Box 89)
          - Brussels Hours, Jacquemart de Hesdin, c.1400, MS.11060-1., 7 (Box 89)
        - Chantilly., 70 (Box 89)
          - Miscellaneous works., 3 (Box 89)
          - Book of Hours of Etienne Chevalier, Fouquet, Jean, c.1415-c.1480., 36 (Box 89)
          - Tres Riches Heures of Jean de Berry, Limbourg Bros., c.1415., 31 (Box 89)
            - Miscellaneous pages., 7 (Box 89)
            - Months., 24 (Box 89)
        - London., 19 (Box 90)
          - Miscellaneous works., 12 (Box 90)
          - Bedford Hours, c.1423., 7 (Box 90)
        - New York., 47 (Box 90)
          - Miscellaneous works., 17 (Box 90)
          - Belles Heures of Jean de Berry, Limbourg Bros., 1410-1413., 30 (Box 90)
        - Paris., 67 (Box 91)
          - Miscellaneous works., 6 (Box 91)
          - Bibliotheque Nationale., 61 (Box 91)
            - Miscellaneous works., 37 (Box 91)
            - Livre de Cleres et Nobles Femmes, Boccaccio, 1403-1404., 11 (Box 91)
            - The Book of Hunting, Gaston Phebus, c.1407, MS fr.616., 5 (Box 91)
            - Les Grandes Heures du Duc de Rohan, Master of the Rohan Hours, c.1435, MS Lat.9471., 8 (Box 91)
        - Vienna., 18 (Box 91)
          - Miscellaneous works., 2 (Box 91)
          - Le Livre du Coeur d'Amour Epris., 16 (Box 91)
      - XVI Century., 14 (Box 91)
    - Germany., 332 (Box 92)
      - Miscellaneous works., 2 (Box 92)
      - IX Century., 40 (Box 92)
      - X Century., 37 (Box 92)
        - Miscellaneous works., 20 (Box 92)
        - Gospels from Klus Cloister, MS 84., 17 (Box 92)
      - XI Century., 61 (Box 93)
        - Miscellaneous works., 47 (Box 93)
        - Bamberg Apocalypse, c.1020., 6 (Box 93)
        - Gospels of Otto III, c.1000., 8 (Box 93)
      - XII Century., 125 (Box 94)
        - Miscellaneous works., 19 (Box 94)
        - Reisenbibel, MS 1., 50 (Box 94)
        - Berthold Missal, MS 710., 56 (Box 95)
      - XIII Century., 23 (Box 96)
      - XIV Century., 16 (Box 96)
      - XV Century., 24 (Box 96)
      - XVI Century., 4 (Box 96)
    - Greece., 1 (Box 97)
    - Holland., 36 (Box 97)
    - Italy., 176 (Box 97)
      - Miscellaneous works., 9 (Box 97)
      - XI Century., 4 (Box 97)
      - XIII Century., 10 (Box 97)
      - XIV Century., 53 (Box 98)
        - Miscellaneous works., 39 (Box 98)
        - Florence., 7 (Box 98)
        - New York., 7 (Box 98)
      - XV Century., 93 (Box 99)
        - Miscellaneous works., 23 (Box 99)
        - New York., 42 (Box 99)
        - Siena., 23 (Box 99)
        - Vienna., 5 (Box 99)
      - XVI Century., 7 (Box 100)
    - Portugal., 1 (Box 100)
    - Russia., 16 (Box 100)
    - Spain., 40 (Box 100)
    - Switzerland., 2 (Box 100)
    - United States., 5 (Box 100)